khoyaa.com 2014-11-23

# Privacy Policy | Khoyaa.com

##  Privacy Policy 

The information that we collect from the user will be covered under our privacy policy as explained below.

Your use of site confirms that you have read and understood our terms of service and provide agreement to our Privacy Policy. We collect your personal information while signing up or posting anything to our site such as your name, email address, phone numbers or any personal preferences that you provide us. We have strict policy not to forward the information so collected to any third party.

As much as possible, do not disclose your personal information to other users. If required you are liable of any consequences.

You further acknowledge and agree that Khoyaa.com in its sole description, preserve or disclose your content as well as your information such as email address, IP address, time stamps, your personal info only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such activity is necessary to comply with legal process or to respond to any copyright claims that any content violates the right of third-parties.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on this site is a violation of our terms of Service and should be reported to us via email or any medium of contacts available.

We may send you email notifications related to our site or the information that might be important to you from time to time. But you may opt out of such email/notifications at anytime through the option available in members area.
